esoacademy.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy » ESO Academy

At ESO Academy, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit ESO Academy, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

## Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.

We also use third party advertisements on ESO Academy to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (Google) information including your IP address, your ISP , and the browser you used to visit our site. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

## DoubleClick DART Cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests.

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. DART does NOT use personally identifiable information. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, however, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. Simply deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

Questions?
